http://glancyhypnosis.com/privacy/

Stress Relief
Home »
Privacy
Privacy
At http://glancyhypnosis.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by http://glancyhypnosis.com and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at admin@glancyhypnosis.com.
Log Files
http://glancyhypnosis.com follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Like any other website, http://glancyhypnosis.com uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.
Our Advertising Partners
Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners include:
Google
Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their website. For easier access, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here:
Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of http://glancyhypnosis.com.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on http://glancyhypnosis.com, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that http://glancyhypnosis.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Part Privacy Policies
http://glancyhypnosis.com’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Children’s Information
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
http://glancyhypnosis.com does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in http://glancyhypnosis.com. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
Recent Posts
Why Wisdom Tooth Extraction Pain Occurs After The Procedure?
How Relaxing Massage Therapy Does Its Magic?
Can Hypnosis Provide Quality Eye Care? (Treatment For Your Eyes)
Which Sedative Drugs For Surgery Can Patients Receive?
Why Regular Exercise Is Positively Related To Wellness (Top 4 Benefits)
Why Wisdom Tooth Extraction Pain Occurs After The Procedure?
Posted by glancy on 11-30-20
0
How Relaxing Massage Therapy Does Its Magic?
Posted by glancy on 10-28-20
0
Can Hypnosis Provide Quality Eye Care? (Treatment For Your Eyes)
Posted by glancy on 10-24-20
0
Which Sedative Drugs For Surgery Can Patients Receive?
Posted by glancy on 8-23-20
0
Why Regular Exercise Is Positively Related To Wellness (Top 4 Benefits)
Posted by glancy on 7-16-20
0
Why You Shouldn’t Be Afraid Of The Dentist (How Hypnosis Can Help)
Posted by glancy on 5-26-20
0
What Things a Sleep Apnea Doctor Near Me Should Know?
Posted by glancy on 3-20-20
0
How Does A General Air Compressor Work?
Posted by glancy on 3-14-20
0
What Are Sedation Procedures From Dentists? (Benefits Of Dental Hypnosis)
What Is Self Hypnosis?
Posted by glancy on 1-23-20
0
How Much Does Hypnotherapy Cost?
How much does sleep dentistry cost?
Does Sleep Hypnosis Really Work?
What Pain Reliever Can I Take Before Surgery?
Posted by glancy on 9-19-19
0
Online Hypnosis: Is it Real?
How effective is hypnosis for ptsd?
Posted by glancy on 7-13-19
0
Getting Started with Hypnotherapy Techniques for Dental Care
Impact of Dental Hypnotherapy Service.
Posted by glancy on 5-12-19
0
Should I get a Nose Job?
Conversational Hypnosis: How words influence your subconscious
Does Hypnosis Work For Weight Loss?
Braces Before and After: How Braces Can Boost Your Confidence
Why Wisdom Tooth Extraction Pain Occurs After The Procedure?
How Relaxing Massage Therapy Does Its Magic?
Can Hypnosis Provide Quality Eye Care? (Treatment For Your Eyes)
Which Sedative Drugs For Surgery Can Patients Receive?
Why Regular Exercise Is Positively Related To Wellness (Top 4 Benefits)
